莫妮卡  你的保时捷能借我吗
Monica? Hey, can I borrow the Porsche?
-好的  -太好了
- Okay.  - All right!
有什么"不准"的呢
But what is it not?
不准在车上和我女性朋友玩乐
A place to entertain my lady friends.
还有什么呢
And what else is it not?
不准在车上吃意大利面
A place to eat spaghetti.
乖  你开车干嘛去
Very good. What do you need it for anyway?
强力球彩票的奖金已经累积到三亿了
The Powerball lottery is up to 300 million...
但是这里又没有卖的
and they don't sell tickets here.
所以你要开车到康涅狄格州去买
So you're driving up to Connecticut?
对  康涅狄格州  不是西弗吉尼亚州
Yeah, Connecticut. Not West Virginia.
也许我可以开车载你去
Maybe I'll drive you up there.
我也想买几张彩票
I'd like to buy some tickets myself.
钱德勒不挣钱  这三亿我们可以用一下
Yeah, with Chandler not getting paid, we could really use $300 million.
是的  如果我还是原来的工作
Yes, because if I was at my old job,
我们会说"三亿元  不用  谢了"
we'd say, ''300 million? No, thank you.''
你可以帮我买吗
Will you get me tickets too?
对啊  我也要
Yeah, me too.
-当然  -我有个主意
- Sure.  - I have an idea.
我们一人拿五十块钱  一起买
Why don't we all pitch in 50 bucks, we'll pool our money together...
如果我们中奖  大家平分
and then if we win, we'll split it.
这主意不错
That's a great idea!
不用  谢了
No, thanks.
你不想要中彩票吗
You don't wanna win the lottery?
我当然想
Sure I do.
我还想当国王呢
I also want to be king of my own country...
我还想知道阿梅莉亚·埃尔哈特怎么了
...and find out what happened to Amelia Earhart.
还在想那个女飞行员吗
Still on Amelia Earhart?
那女人就那样消失了
The woman just vanished!
说真的  你真的不加入吗
Seriously, you don't want in on this?
不要  你们知道
No. Do you know what
中彩票的机率有多大吗
your odds are of winning the lottery?
比你被雷劈四十二次的机率还小
I mean, you have a better chance of being struck by lightning 42 times.
但是我们有六个人
But there's six of us,
所以我们只需要被打到七次
so we'd only have to get struck 7 times.
我喜欢这种机率
I like those odds!
真的  你们  我不敢相信
Seriously, you guys, I can't believe
你们居然花了两百五十块买彩票
you're gonna spend $250 on the lottery.
这实在太狗便便了吧
I mean, that's such a bunch of boo-hockey.
我来问
I'll ask.
狗便便
''Boo-hockey''?
艾玛已经要开始学说话了
Oh, we think Emma's about to start talking...
所以我们在她面前会注意用词
...so we're trying to be careful about what words we use in front of her.
准备好吧  你们会听到很多的狗便便
So get ready to hear a lot of boo-hockey...
"去安息吧"还有"她母亲的"等等
...gosh darn it and brother pucker.
你怎么知道她要开始说话了
How do you know she's gonna start talking?
我跟她说话的时候
When I talk to her,
我似乎感觉到  她好像能听懂
I almost feel like she understands what I'm saying.
有点像乔伊
Kind of like Joey.
你说什么
What's that now?
《老友记》  第九季 第18集  彩票啊彩票
Friends S09E18 The One With The Lottery
天啊  瞧瞧这些彩票  激动人心啊
God, look at all these tickets. It's so exciting.
自从六年级后
I haven't won anything
我就没有赢过任何东西了
since sixth grade.
吃派大赛吗
Pie-eating contest?
因为我原来很胖
You assume because I was heavy
你就以为那是我唯一能赢的比赛吗
that's the only way I could win something?
不  我看过你全身都是蓝莓的照片
No, I saw a picture of you covered in blueberries.
-那天还真开心啊  -是啊
- That was a good day.  - Yeah.
他们要把你的车拖走了
They're towing your car!
我车停在莫顿的车库里
I'm parked in a garage on Morton.
他们要把一辆车拖走了
They're towing a car.
而我眼冒金星了
And I am seeing spots.
罗斯  你没带艾玛
Ross, you don't have Emma!
瑞秋  你也没有在带艾玛
Rachel, you don't have Emma!
艾玛呢  艾玛到哪去了
Where's Emma? Who has Emma?
乔伊  别紧张
Joey, relax.
两小时前  我妈把她接走了  你也在啊
My mother picked her up two hours ago. You were there.
有吗
I was?
是的  你还跟她说话
Yes, and you talked to her.
-我有吗  -她还带来了砂锅菜来
- I did?  - She dropped off a casserole.
对  那个砂锅夫人
Oh, yeah, the casserole lady.
你是过来看我们中大奖的吗
Did you come by to watch us win the big bucks?
是啊  我还想在你们中奖后
Yeah. And then I figured after you win,
全部到阳台上
we can all go out to the balcony...
看小精灵在夜之彩虹上跳舞
and see a night rainbow with gremlins dancing on top of it.
别碰电话  我来接
Don't touch the phone! I'll get it!
-你觉得他有洗手吗  -你好
- You think he washed his hands?  - Hello?
查理  有什么消息
Hey, Charlie, what do you know?
怎么回事
What's going on?
他们公司开始决定雇佣谁了
Chandler's supposed to find out
钱德勒在等消息
if he's getting a job at his agency.
但在十五名实习生中
But out of 15 interns,
他们只聘请三个人
they're only hiring three.
-机率真小  -是啊
- Tough odds.  - Yeah.
像你们二十四州联合彩票的
If only it were a sure thing
机率一样高
like your 24-state lottery.
是啊  瞧瞧谁想通了
Yeah, look who's coming around!
该死  好啦  有消息再通知我
Damn it. All right, call me when you know more.
-用你了吗  -一个名额已经被占了
- Did you get it?  - One of the slots got filled.
-被你吗  -听话听音
- By you?  - Sense the tone.
不是我  是个叫内特的小子
No, that kid Nate got it.
喔  我讨厌那小子
Oh, I hate that guy.
真想说  有没有搞错
I mean, come on,
小子  把裤子提上去
kid, pull up your pants!
还有两个名额不是吗
Well, there's two spots left, right?
是  我真的好想要  我想要被录取
Yeah. I mean, I want this so much. I wanna get one.
也希望我朋友查理被录取
I want my friend Charlie to get one.
其实我不是很在乎查理
Except I don't care about Charlie.
-嘿  你们好  -嘿
- Hey, you guys.  - Hey!
你们不会相信的
You are not gonna believe this.
我刚刚遇到我的算命师傅
I just saw my psychic.
她说我今晚一定会中彩票的
and she said I was definitely gonna win the lottery tonight!
提醒我了  我想要增加好运
That's reminds me.I thought we could use some extra luck...
所以从餐厅带了个幸运骨头回来
...so I brought a wishbone home from work.
算命师傅再加上幸运骨头
A psychic and a wishbone?
拜托给别人留点机会吧
Guys, give someone else a chance.
好了  谁来
All right, who wants to do it?
我可以吗
Can I?
素食者从来就没机会玩幸运骨头
Vegetarians never get to do the wishbone.
特别不公平  我们只是不吃肉
It's really not fair. Just because we don't eat the meat...
不代表我们不喜欢玩尸骨
...doesn't mean we don't like to play with the carcasses.
好了  瑞秋呢
All right. Rach?
我不想要让手沾上火鸡的味道
I don't want that turkey smell all over my hands.
我来  我要把砂锅菜的味道盖过去
I'll do it! It'll get the casserole stink off of mine.
-希望我会赢  -嗯  没有关系
- I hope I win.  - Well, it doesn't really matter.
你们的愿望是一样的
You're both wishing for the same thing.
我不能告诉你我许什么愿
I can't tell you what I'm wishing for,
要不然不会实现的
or else, you know, it won't come true.
对  但是我们都知道你许什么愿
Right. But we know what you're wishing for.
-我真不能讲出来  -我了解
- I can't really say.  - I understand.
但你许的愿跟我们想的一样  不是吗
But you're wishing for what we think, aren't you?
我真的很不喜欢这些问题
I'm not really comfortable with these questions!
-拜托  -赶快做
- Please!  - Just do it!
好的  一  二  三
Okay. One, two, three.
我赢了  嘿
I won! Hey!
你们知道吗
You know what?
我确定你们的愿望会成真
I'm sure your wish is gonna come true.
但是  为了以防万一
But, you guys, just in case,
我们来擦这个灯  或许灯神会出现
maybe a genie will come out if we rub this lamp.
那东西好烫啊
That thing gets hot!
罗斯  你可以继续取笑我们
Ross, just keep making your jokes.
万一我们真中奖了  你怎么想
How are you gonna feel if we actually do win?
你们不会中的
You're not gonna win.
我知道机率很小
I know the odds are against us...
但是总是有人会中
...but somebody has to win,
也有可能是我们  到时候你怎么想
and it could be us. And then how you gonna feel?
我们会说"大家开直升机去海岬玩吧"
We're gonna be like, ''Everybody, let's take our helicopters up to the Cape.''
而你只能说  我不行…
And you're gonna be all, like, ''Oh, I can't, guys.
待会见好了  我得给我的现代加油
I'll have to meet you up there. I gotta gas up the Hyundai.''
够了  我听过自己的录音
Okay, I've heard myself on tape,
根本不是这样的
and I sound nothing like that.
到时候头条新闻是这样的
I can see the headline now:
"因见好友们中彩票
''Lottery Winners' Friend,
懊悔不已   自食手臂"
Filled With Regret, Eats Own Arm.''
我为什么要吃自己的手臂
Why would I eat my own arm?
你当然不会
Well, you wouldn't,
但我们可以买下那报社  爱怎么写就怎么写
but we own the paper. We can print whatever we want.
你知道吗  我帮你出五十块好了
You know what? I'm gonna throw in 50 bucks for you.
-为什么  -因为我知道你认为
- Why?  - Because I know that you think...
彩票是很狗便便的东西
that the lottery is boo-hockey...
但大家在一起等着开奖  会很好玩的
...but we're all here, and we're gonna watch the numbers and have fun.
你是我哥  我希望你也有份
And you're my brother, and I want you to be a part of this.
你不用这样  我自己付钱好了
You don't have to do that. I mean, I'll pay for myself.
你想让我和你们一起开心
But just the fact that you want me to have fun with you guys,
真的是太窝心了
that's so sweet.
过来
Come here.
开房去吧
Get a room.
你已经加入了
So now that you're in,
要是中奖了  你会干嘛
what are you gonna do if we win?
我不知道  或许投资吧
I don't know. I'll probably just invest it.
你能再冷静点吗
Calm down.
正经点  这就是你的白日梦
Seriously, that's your fantasy?
就是投资
To invest it?
我很抱歉  我是说投资吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I say, ''invest it''?
我的意思是"快乐的全部花光光"
I meant, ''Be cool and piss it all away.''
我知道了  我们该把全部的钱凑起来
I know! We should pool all our money
买下尼克斯队
and buy the Knicks!
我不是很在乎尼克斯队
I don't really care about the Knicks.
如果我选你当前锋  你就会了
You will when I pick you as starting forward.
你会那样做吗  我从没有被选上
You would do that? I never get picked!
我不确定球队会是正确的选择
I'm not sure a sports team is the way to go.
你不让我买尼克斯队吗
You won't let me buy the Knicks?
不敢相信你要打破我的梦想
I can't believe you're taking this away.
你说的对  这个梦想已经有十五秒之久了
You're right, it has been your dream for over 15 seconds.
还要多久才会摇奖  妈咪
How long until they announce the numbers, Mommy?
这个也让我来  "妈咪"
I'll take this one too. ''Mommy''?
喔  我要习惯叫瑞秋"妈咪"
Oh, I've gotten into the habit of calling Rachel...
只要是艾玛在场
...''Mommy'' when we're around Emma.
我现在发现她并不在
Which I now realize we are not.
希望她听久了  她第一句话会说这个
I'm hoping that if she hears it enough, it'll be her first word.
如果真的要这样做
Although if we're gonna do that,
你也应该叫我"爹地"才对
we should probably call me ''Daddy'' too.
我喜欢哦  爹地
I like that, Daddy.
我只是在说瑞秋
I was just talking about Rachel.
爹地生气了吗
Is Daddy getting angry?
爹地要打我吗
Is Daddy gonna spank me?
嗯  那要看
Well, that depends.
你是不是不乖...
Have you been a bad--?
不行  我演不下去
No, I can't.
哈啰  嘿  查理  还有其他人吗
Hello? Hello? Hey, Charlie. Did anybody else hear?
什么  苏珊拿到了  怎么会呢
What? Susan got it? How?
喔  天啊  早知道我也跟他上床
Oh, man, I would've slept with him!
好了  拜
All right, bye.
老兄  我很抱歉
Dude, I'm sorry. But hey,
还有一个名额  不是吗
there's one spot left, right?
那也是查理的
Well, Charlie's gonna get that.
别那样说
Hey, don't say that.
你也有一样的机会
You've got just as good a chance of getting that job.
他是老板的儿子
He is the boss' son.
-来吧  彩票  -是啊
- Come on, lottery!  - Yeah!
大概二十分钟就开奖了
It starts in, like, 20 minutes.
好了  我们来吧
Okay, here we go.
我们需要尽快分配这些彩票对奖
We need to sort through the tickets quickly to see if we've won.
谁有主意要怎么安排吗
So does anybody have any ideas how to organize this?
好的  这样如何
Okay, how about this:
我们分成六组各四十张
We divide them into six groups of 40.
剩下的十张就由先对完的人来对
The remaining 10 can be read by whoever finishes first.
我还有一个主意
I have another idea.
很抱歉  提议时间已经过了
I'm sorry, idea time is over.
-所有的彩票都在碗里了吗  -是的
- Well, are all the tickets in the bowl?  - Yeah.
那床头柜上面的那些呢
What about the ones on the nightstand?
那边没有彩票
There are no tickets there.
那边有  我几分钟前才看到
Yes, there are. I just saw them a few minutes ago.
不对  没有  你看错了
No, you didn't. You must be mistaken.
床头柜上有二十张彩票
There are 20 tickets on the nightstand.
钱德勒  听话听音
Chandler, sense the tone.
哎呦喂  瞧瞧妈咪找到了什么
Well, well, well. Look what Mommy found.
好啦  我给自己和钱德勒多买了二十张
Okay, fine. I bought 20 extra tickets for me and Chandler.
算命的还说我会被朋友背叛
The psychic also said that I would be betrayed.
我不敢相信  我以为我们是一起的
I can't believe this. I thought we were all in this together.
你五分钟前才加入的
Hey, you just got in five minutes ago!
是三分钟前
Three minutes ago!
我不知道那有什么重要的
I don't know why that's important.
我们一直在一起
I was with you the whole time.
你是什么时候买的
When did you even get those?
就在你看未拆封的色情书刊的时候
When you were reading the dirty magazines without taking off the plastic.
我教你
I'll show you how.
好了  莫妮卡
Okay. Well, Monica,
假设你的额外彩票中奖了怎么办
suppose one of your special tickets wins?
你中了彩票但失去了朋友  你怎么办
How are you gonna feel when you win and lose your friends?
拜托  如果我中奖了
Please. If I win the lottery,
你们才不会离开我
you guys are not gonna leave me.
上星期有人给我些小松饼
Someone gave me muffins last week,
就让你们骚扰了我整整三天
and I couldn't get rid of you for three days!
钱德勒  你可以告诉她这是不对的吗
Chandler, would you just tell her what she did was wrong?
她说得对
She's right.
你不应该帮我们两个另买彩票
You shouldn't have bought tickets just for us.
让我说完
Let me finish.
然而  看起来我好像得不到这份工作了
However, it doesn't look like I'm gonna get this job...
原则太贵  承受不起
...so I can't afford to have principles.
所以  去你们的  彩票是我们的
So screw you! The tickets are ours!
我嫁了个好男人
There's the man I married.
好了  相信我  如果你们中奖了
All right. Believe me, if you win the lottery
我们不再是朋友
it's the last you're gonna hear from us.
无所谓  不用你们当朋友
Fine. Don't be my friends.
我会买新朋友
I'll buy new friends.
是的  我还会付钱让他们做整形手术
Yeah, and then I'll pay for their plastic surgery
变得跟你们一模一样
so they look just like you!
你知道吗  我要拿回我的份
You know what? I want my share of the tickets.
我也要拿回我的
I want my tickets too!
而且我要买下尼克斯队
And I'm buying the Knicks!
还有施特菲·格拉芙（德国网球运动员）
And Steffi Graf!
太好了  那我也要拿回我的
Cool. Then I want mine too!
如果我中奖…
And if I win...
我要拿全部的钱去买低利公债
I'm gonna put it all into a very low-yield bond!
不行  我们必须要把彩票放在一起
No. You guys, we gotta keep all the tickets together.
不  我们应该分一分
No. No, we should divide them up...
而且我应该多分点
...and I should get extra
因为是开我的车买的
because we used my car!
如果有人可以多拿一些
Hey! Hey! If anybody gets extra tickets,
那也应该是我
it should be me!
这整件事都是我想出来的
This whole thing was my idea!
是啊  谢谢你发明彩票
Yeah. Thanks for inventing the lottery!
把彩票给我  我来分
Just give them to me, and I'll split them up!
嘿  嘿
Hey, hey!
天啊  我再也受不了了
God, I can't take it anymore!
我来结束这一切
I'm putting an end to this!
如果她跳楼了  她的彩票就是我的
Okay, if she jumps, I get her tickets!
等等  不  嘿
Wait, no, no! Hey!
要么同进退  要么一切归零
If we're not doing this together, we're not doing it at all.
跟你们的彩票说再见吧
Say goodbye to your tickets.
不  不  不
No! No! No!
不要再靠近过来了
Do not come any closer!
我可以再靠近一点点吗
Can I come a little bit closer?
我的宝贝被压到了
Valuable things are getting squished.
现在  什么比较重要
Now, what's more important,
朋友还是钱
your friends or money?
-朋友  -钱
- Friends!  - Money!
朋友
Friends.
嘿  莫妮卡  那你额外的彩票呢
Hey, Monica, what about your extra tickets?
全都在里面了
They're all in there.
还有我内衣藏的这五张
Even these five that I hid in my bra.
莫妮卡
Monica!
好的  很好  你们都吓坏了
Okay. Good. You guys were so scared.
我才不会丢掉这些...
There is no way I was gonna dump this--
天啊  不
God! No!
我好像把你的碗摔破了
I think I broke your bowl.
快快快
Go! Go! Go!
多美好的夜晚啊  到街上去找彩票
What a beautiful night to be running around the street, looking for tickets.
而且被风一吹就更有趣了
And the wind sure made it fun.
菲比  有一半不见了
Phoebe, we lost half of them.
那又怎样
So what?
莫妮卡  我们还是会中奖的
Monica, we have the winning ticket.
算命师傅说我会中奖的  记得吗
My psychic said I was gonna win, remember?
奇怪的是
Weird your psychic didn't mention
算命师没算到可怕的鸽子
anything about the scary pigeon.
她有说过  我就是那么死的
As a matter of fact, she said that's how I'm going to die.
所以  原谅我有点被吓到
So excuse me for being a little skittish.
有两通留言  可能是工作的消息
There's two messages. This could be from work.
-放出来  -好了  来了
- Oh, play them.  - Okay. Here we go.
你好  我是阳台上的鸽子
Hello. This is the pigeon from the balcony
打电话过来道歉的
calling to apologize.
我不应该把彩票
I shouldn't have knocked the tickets
从那个漂亮小姐手中弄翻
out of the pretty lady's hand.
全是我的错  不关她的事  拜
It was all my fault. Not hers. Bye.
嗯  他这道歉能做到一定很难
Well, I bet that was very hard for him to do.
嘿  钱德勒  我是查理
Hey, Chandler, it's Charlie.
就是这个了
This is it.
听着  结果最后的名额给我了
Listen, it turns out I got the last spot.
我很抱歉  老兄  很高兴跟你共事过
I'm really sorry, man. It was a lot of fun working with you.
再打电话给我吧
Give me a call if you want.
天啊  我很难过  亲爱的
Gosh, I'm so sorry, honey.
真替你难过  钱德勒
Sorry, Chandler.
这真是不公平  这就像那次
It is so unfair. It's like that time
他们升珊卓  而不是我一样
they promoted Saundra over me at work.
她跟拉夫·劳伦是亲戚吗
Was she related to Ralph Lauren?
不是  只是她工作能力比我强太多了
No, she was just much better at her job than me.
你们大家  快要开奖了
You guys, the drawing's about to start.
我们应该打电话给我妈
We should call my mom's
跟艾玛说晚安
and say good night to Emma...
-趁她还没睡着  -好主意
- before she goes down.  - Good idea.
亲爱的  这件事上你真的很坚强
Honey, you're being really strong about this.
我知道你很想要这份工作
I know how badly you wanted that job.
是啊  我觉得本来是我应得的
Yeah, you know, I really thought I deserved it.
让我们来赢彩票吧
But let's go win the lottery.
我们还有一百三十个机会  不是吗
I mean, we still have a 130 chances to win, right?
一百三十一个
Hundred and thirty-one.
是的  晚安甜心  我爱你
Yeah, good night, sweetheart. I love you.
还有记住  你是爹地的小乖女
And remember, you're Daddy's little girl.
菲比完全毁了这感觉
Phoebe's totally ruined that for me.
嗨  妈  让艾玛听
Hi, Mom. Put her back on.
瑞秋  他们在开奖了
Rach, they're announcing the numbers!
我的天啊  我可以感到自己在改变了
My God, I can already feel myself changing.
强力球彩票中奖号码  有五十三
Here are your official Powerball numbers. We have 53.
-我有  -我们也有一个
- I've got that.  - We have one too!
我们快中奖了
We are on the road, people!
快点
Come on!
妈  拜托
Mom, please,
我知道你喜欢你的新嘴唇
I know you love your new lips,
但是我听不太懂你说什么
but I can barely understand you.
可以让我跟我女儿道晚安吗
Would you please just let me say good night to my daughter?
然后接下来的号码是七
And here we go. The Powerball is seven.
好了  你们快对号码  让我发财吧
All right, check your numbers! Make me rich.
你们大家  你们不会相信这个的
You guys, you're not gonna believe this.
我刚刚在跟艾玛说晚安的时候
I was just saying good night to Emma,
她说了第一个单词
and she said her first words.
-什么  -她说了什么
- What?  - Well, what did she say?
她说了"葛利巴"
She said, ''Gleba'' !
让我发财吧
Make me rich!
是不是很惊人呢
Isn't that amazing?
是啊  真是太棒了
Oh, yeah. No, no, no, that's great.
你怎么会不兴奋呢
Why aren't you more excited?
瑞秋  "葛利巴"不算单词
Rach, gleba is not a word.
它当然算
Well, of course it is.
好吧  那它是什么意思呢
Okay. What does it mean?
我又不认识所有的字词
Well, I don't know all the words.
我很高兴没有错过我女儿开口讲话
You know, I'm just glad I didn't miss my daughter's first word.
你就是错过了  "葛利巴"算
Yes you did! Gleba is a word!
好的  那用它造句
Okay. Use it in a sentence.
好的  艾玛刚刚说了"葛利巴"
Okay. Emma just said, ''Gleba.''
那不算说话
It's not a word.
好的  我来查字典
Okay, fine. I'm gonna look it up.
好的  太好了
Okay, great.
顺便查一下  有天她说的另外一句
While you're at it, she said another word the other day.
你何不也查查看这个
Why don't you look up:
好了  葛利巴...
All right. Okay. Okay. Gleba...
找到了  "含孢子的丰厚菌种"
Here it is! ''The fleshy, spore-bearing inner mass of a certain fungi.''
她会成为科学家的
She's gonna be a scientist.
-该死的  有人有对到吗  -没有
- Damn it. Anybody got anything?  - No.
我还在对我的
I'm still looking through mine.
再对一次  没有
Just double-checking. No.
没有  没有
No. No.
没有
No!
你好  等一下
Hello? Hold on.
是你老板
It's your boss.
"拒绝你了  很抱歉"的电话来了
The ''I'm sorry I rejected you'' phone call.
我还真不习惯男生打这种电话来
I'm not used to getting these from guys.
-嘿  史提夫  -钱德勒  嗨
- Hey, Steve.  - Chandler, hi.
我想你已经听说  我们三个名额都满了
I'm sure you've heard we filled the three positions.
我们觉得以你的成熟度及经验
We felt that with your maturity and experience...
你不会甘心当个助理而已的
you wouldn't be happy being someone's assistant.
我爱死当助理了  接听电话…
I'd love to be somebody's assistant. Answering phones...
倒咖啡  我就是为那些工作而活的
...getting coffee, I live for that stuff.
而且我并没有很成熟
And I'm not too mature.
放屁  咪咪  屁蛋
Farts, boobies, butt cracks!
钱德勒  你是全部的人里面最优秀的
Chandler, you were the strongest person in the program.
我们要聘请你当初级广告文案
We're offering you the position of junior copywriter.
我  那个刚刚才说"屁蛋"的人
Me? That guy who just said, ''butt cracks''?
是的  没错
Yes, that's right.
我们很期望你能带给这份工作…
We're excited about the level of sophistication...
一定程度的深度
...you'll be bringing to the job.
好的  谢谢  你不会失望的  明天见
Okay. Well, thanks, you won't regret it. I'll see you tomorrow.
怎么了
What?
对  我要当初级广告文案了
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be a junior copywriter.
恭喜了  亲爱的  为你骄傲
Congratulations! Oh, sweetie, I'm so proud of you.
谢谢  这表示我今晚可以被爱爱吗
Thanks. Does that mean I get the good loving tonight?
当然  不看电视或什么其它的
You bet. No TV or anything.
嘿  恭喜你找到工作了
Hey, that is so great about the job.
谢了  老兄
Thanks, man.
我其实也有帮到忙
I'd like to think I had something to do with it.
真的吗  怎么说
Really? Why?
刚刚在玩幸运骨头的时候…
Well, before with the wishbone.
我没有许愿我们中彩票
I didn't wish we would win the lottery.
我的愿望是你找到工作
I wished you'd get the job.
喔  是吗
Oh, yeah?
听着  别告诉莫妮卡  她会把五马分尸的
Listen, don't tell Monica. She'll rip your heart right out.
你们知道吗  我刚刚真有一点感觉
Well, you know what? There was a little part of me...
我们会中奖
...that really thought we were gonna win.
我也是  都是为了我的
Me too. So much for my
恐龙与女飞行员主题公园
dinosaur/ Amelia Earhart theme park.
中奖号码是多少来着
You guys? What was the Powerball number again?
-七  -我们中奖了
- Seven.  - We won.
-什么  -我们中奖了
- What?  - We won!
-让我看  让我看 -别撕掉了
-Let me see! Let me see! -Don't tear it!
菲比  你其它五个号码都不对
Phoebe, you don't have any of the first five numbers!
我知道  但是我们中了特别号
I know that, but look, we got the Powerball number.
我们中了三块钱
We won $3!
哇  你觉得我们应该分二十年提领
Wow, you think we should get that over 20 years
还是一次领光呢
or go for the big payout?
我不管  我从来就没有中过任何东西
I don't care. I've never won anything before.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this!
菲比  你要怎么花这三块钱呢
So, Pheebs, what are you gonna do with your $3?
又不是全都是我的
Well, it's not all mine.
我们每个人都有五十分
We all get 50 cents.
你知道吗  我那份给你
You know what? You can have mine.
-我的也是  -我的也是
- Me too.  - Me too.
我的也是
Me too.
好吧  既然大家都要给你
Well, I guess if everybody else is.
嘿  我刚刚打了彩票热线
Hey, guys. So I just called the Powerball hot line.
你们敢相信吗  没有人中奖耶
Can you believe it? Nobody won.
恕我不能赞同
I beg to differ.
或许没有人中头奖
Maybe nobody won the jackpot,
但是刚刚这里有个人
but there was this guy in here earlier...
在外面捡到一张彩票
...and he found a ticket on the street right outside
中了一万块钱
and won $ 10,000.
不要再责怪漂亮小姐了
Again, don't blame the pretty lady.
那不是她的错  是鸽子我的错
It was not her fault. It was me, the pigeon.
真的  不要再瞪她了
Seriously, stop staring at her.